ADAM HAVIV

ashaviv27@gmail.com

050-818-1126

github.com/ashvv1

in linkedin.com/in/adam-haviv-84bb17225/

https://www.adamhaviv.com

Profile

More than one year experience working on professional and personal projects.

Fast learning and initiative-taking autodidact with English as a first language.

Has experience in planning, prototyping, and developing a product from the ground up. Very passionate about learning and creating. Looking for a Full Stack, Front End or Back End Developer position which will allow me to utilize my relevant experience as well as grow as a developer.

Technical Knowledge/Experience

- Databases: MongoDB, Firestore, mySQL
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Next.js, jQuery
- **DevOps/Workflow**: Docker, GitHub, Jira, Jenkins, EC2, ECR, Netlify, Heroku
- Cloud: AWS (EC2), Firebase, Mongo Atlas
- Web3: Solidity, Web3 Integrations
- Back-End: Node.JS, Express, PHP
- Testing: Jenkins, Mocha

Professional Experience

April 2	023 -	Present
---------	-------	---------

Software Developer, Cambium LTD.

- Currently working on a project to automate the QA testing process for a client using TypeScript, Puppeteer and Mocha.
- Was responsible for producing custom WordPress websites and Plugins with PHP and Elementor.
- **Soft Skills:** Flexibility, Willingness to learn new technologies from my peers, problem solving.
- Technologies: Typescript, PHP, HTML, jQuery, Jenkins, Testrail

August 2022 - April 2023

Full-Stack Developer (Intern), Minerva XR

- Worked as part of a small team of Full Stack Developers to develop a Learning Management System as well as solutions using Body Tracking.
- **Soft Skills:** Team work, **prototyping**, debugging, planning and implementation of LMS; managed **AWS** services (EC2, ECR) **and updated Docker images**; produced true to **Figma** frontend for LMS, frequent code reviews; Maintained API
- **Technologies**: Firestore/Firebase, React.js, Node.js

October 2022 - June 2023

Python Instructor, Nitzanim Program

- **Teaching** 10th graders Python while following a strict syllabus intended to prepare students for Army service in cyber units.
- **Soft skills:** Relaying complicated concepts in a simplified manner to high school students while developing their coding and problem-solving skills.

Education

January 2022 – June 2022

SV College

- Fullstack Development Program
- Focus on MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node)

October 2021 – January 2022

Codecademy

- Certificate of completion (Front-End Development)
- Certificate of completion (JavaScript)

Languages

^{*}Familiarity with: Python, Java